<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:padding="@dimen/standard_spacing">

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/products_details_popup_iv"
        android:layout_width="200dp"
        android:layout_height="200dp"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        android:src="@drawable/ic_product_placeholder" />

    <EditText
        android:id="@+id/products_details_popup_txt_title"
        style="@style/EditTextAdminToggle"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_marginTop="@dimen/standard_separating_margin"
        android:gravity="center"
        android:textColor="@color/text_color_dark"
        android:textSize="@dimen/title_text_size"
        android:textStyle="bold"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/products_details_popup_iv"
        tools:ignore="TouchTargetSizeCheck"
        tools:text="the title" />

    <EditText
        android:id="@+id/products_details_popup_txt_categories"
        style="@style/EditTextAdminToggle"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:textSize="@dimen/small_text_size"
        android:textStyle="bold"
        android:gravity="center"
        android:textColor="@color/text_color_light"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/products_details_popup_txt_title"
        android:layout_marginTop="@dimen/standard_separating_margin"
        tools:text="category1, category2, category3" />

    <LinearLayout
        android:id="@+id/linearLayout3"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="horizontal"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/products_details_popup_txt_categories"
        android:layout_marginTop="@dimen/standard_separating_margin"
        >
        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:textColor="@color/text_color_dark"
            android:textSize="@dimen/standard_text_size"
            android:text="@string/dollar_sign" />

        <EditText
            android:id="@+id/products_details_popup_txt_price"
            style="@style/EditTextAdminToggle"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:textColor="@color/text_color_dark"
            android:textSize="@dimen/standard_text_size"
            tools:ignore="TouchTargetSizeCheck"
            tools:text="4.99" />

    </LinearLayout>

    <Button
        android:backgroundTint="@color/standard_btn_bg"
        android:id="@+id/products_details_popup_btn_back"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:text="@string/btn_generic_back"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        android:layout_marginTop="@dimen/standard_separating_margin"
        />

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scrollView2"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_marginTop="@dimen/standard_separating_margin"
        android:fillViewport="true"
        android:scrollbars="vertical"
        app:layout_constrainedHeight="true"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toTopOf="@+id/products_details_popup_admin_buttons_group"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/linearLayout3">

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <EditText
                android:id="@+id/products_details_popup_txt_desc"
                style="@style/EditTextAdminToggle"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:scrollbars="vertical"
                android:textColor="@color/text_color_light"
                android:textSize="@dimen/standard_text_size"
                tools:text="this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. this is the kind of long description of the product titled above. Let's write a few sentences to see how it looks. That should just about do it. " />

        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>

    <ImageButton
        android:id="@+id/products_details_popup_btn_edit_image"
        android:layout_width="50dp"
        android:layout_height="50dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="@+id/products_details_popup_iv"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="@+id/products_details_popup_iv"
        app:srcCompat="@drawable/ic_edit"
        android:visibility="gone"
        android:scaleType="fitCenter"
        android:backgroundTint="@android:color/transparent"
        tools:ignore="SpeakableTextPresentCheck" />


    <LinearLayout
        android:id="@+id/products_details_popup_admin_buttons_group"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="horizontal"
        android:visibility="gone"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toTopOf="@+id/products_details_popup_btn_back"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/scrollView2">

        <Button
            android:backgroundTint="@color/standard_btn_bg"
            android:id="@+id/products_details_popup_btn_delete"
            android:layout_width="0dp"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:layout_margin="@dimen/standard_separating_margin"
            android:layout_weight="1"
            android:text="@string/products_details_popup_btn_delete" />

        <Button
            android:backgroundTint="@color/standard_btn_bg"
            android:id="@+id/products_details_popup_btn_save"
            android:layout_width="0dp"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:layout_margin="@dimen/standard_separating_margin"
            android:layout_weight="1"
            android:text="@string/products_details_popup_btn_save" />

        <Button
            android:backgroundTint="@color/standard_btn_bg"
            android:id="@+id/products_details_popup_btn_reset"
            android:layout_width="0dp"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:layout_margin="@dimen/standard_separating_margin"
            android:layout_weight="1"
            android:text="@string/products_details_popup_btn_reset" />


    </LinearLayout>


</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>